Folks I like to sleep in.
I love to get that extra wing.
But oh how much more important
it is to get up and pray.
Prince spend time with
the Lord in prayer.
I remember Christ in the garden.
when he
finds them asleep in
Matthew finds the Disciples
of sleep in Matthew 26,
and it's interesting. It says
in verse 40 of Matthew 26,
they come with it
to Disciples of finding them
asleep and sayeth unto Peter.
What could you not watch
with me one hour?
In the instant, he doesn't
say it to all the disciples.
Peter could you not watch
with me one hour why
Peter Well Peter was the
one to say oh everybody pray for
sakes you I won't forsake you.
And Peter was an hour away
from denying the
Lord.
You know, maybe.
Maybe if Peter had been praying
instead of sleeping.
He would have had the faith
to stand up to the maiden and to
the others and say yes.
I know him. He's my Lord,
but instead he denied.
Redeeming the time through prayer